Society of Southwest Archivists records, Inclusive: 1970-2017, Bulk: 1973-1993, 2003-2016
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Committee Documents, 1972-2017, undated; 2
  - Local Arrangements Committee, 1984-2013, undated; 13
    - Financial: General, 2003-2005 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Financial: General, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Financial: Reception at Oklahoma History Center, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Financial: Past Hotel Agreements, 2011-2012 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Financial and Literary, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Agenda, 2006 March 3 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Literary: "Annual Meeting Planning Guide", circa 1998 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Assignments, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Literary: General, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Literary: General, 1988-2001, undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Hotel Information, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Meeting Plan (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Meeting Plan (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1987-1993 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1994-1996 July (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1996 September-1997 January (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1997 March (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Notes, 1990-2001, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Presentation, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Registration Notes, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Reports, 1991-2008 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Rosters and Volunteer Materials, 2008-2013 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Website Posts, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - 2007 Oklahoma City Meeting: Correspondence (1 of 2), 2005-2007 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - 2007 Oklahoma City Meeting: Correspondence (2 of 2), 2005-2007 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - 2007 Oklahoma City Meeting: Literary: General, 2005-2007 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - 2007 Oklahoma City Meeting: Literary: Hotel Information, 2006-2007 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - 2007 Oklahoma City Meeting: Literary: Program and Panel Materials (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Correspondence, 2011-2012 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Correspondence and Financial Documents: Social Events, Transportation, and Tours Sub-Committee, 2012 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Financial Documents, 2011-2013 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Agendas and Minutes, 2010-2013 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Articles and Maps Concerning Austin, 2012-2013, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Drafts: Procedure Manual, 2011-2013 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Exhibits/Sponsorship Sub-Committee, 2012-2013, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Guide: "Planning an Annual Meeting", 2003-2011 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Hotel Information (1 of 2), 2011-2013 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Hotel Information (2 of 2), 2011-2013 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Notes, 2011-2013, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: PowerPoint Presentations, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: PowerPoint Slides, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Program Materials, 2011-2013 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Registration and Schedule Materials, 2008-2013 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Registration Statistics, 2009-2013 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Reports, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Reports, 2013, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - 2013 Austin Meeting: Literary: Title, Theme, and Logo Materials, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Digital Media: Arizona State University Workshop, undated (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Digital Media: Correspondence, undated (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - Artifact: Ribbon: "Local Arrangements", undated (Box 48 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Artifact: Stamp: Arizona, undated (Box 48 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Membership Committee, 1972-2001, undated; 14
    - Correspondence, 1972-1975 January (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1975 February-March (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1975 April-May (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1975 June-July (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1975 August-September (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1975 October-November 11 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1975 November 19-December (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1976 January-February (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1976 February (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1976 March-April (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1976 May-August (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1976 September-October (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1976 November-1977 February (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1977 March-July (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1977 August-November (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1978 January-March (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1978 April (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1978 June-1979 June (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1979 July-1980 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 January (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1988 February-May (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1988 June (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1988 July 5-8 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1988 July 11-19 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1988 July 20-29 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1988 August 1-15 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1988 August 12-19 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1988 August 22-26 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1988 August 29-31 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1988 September 1-6 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1988 September 7-13 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1988 September 14-21 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1988 October 4 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1988 October 6 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1988 October 6-10 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1988 October 11-17 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1988 October 18-28 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1988 November 1-11 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, 1988 November 14-15 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1988 November 16-28 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 1988 November 29-30 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, 1988 December 5-12 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1988 December 13-29 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1989 January 3-6 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1989 January 12-31 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1989 February 1-20 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1989 February 21-March 17 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1989 March 21-31 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1989 April-May 18 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1989 May 26-July (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1989 July 26-September (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1989 October-December 14 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1989 December 18-19 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1990 January-February 14 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1990 February 15-March (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1990 May-1993 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Shelly Kelly (1 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Shelly Kelly (2 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence and Notices, 1984-1990, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Financial: General, 1989, undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Directories, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Directories (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Directories (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Literary: General, 1972-1996 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Literary: General, undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Membership Directory (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Membership Directory (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Literary: Membership Lists, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Literary: Membership Lists, 1975 January-April (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Literary: Membership Lists, 1975 June (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Membership Lists, 1975 October (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Membership Lists, 1975 December-1976 January (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Membership Lists, 1976 February-March (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Membership Lists, 1976 May (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Membership Lists, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Membership Lists, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Membership Lists (1 of 3), undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Membership Lists (2 of 3), undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Membership Lists (3 of 3), undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Membership Lists: Non-Texas, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Officer Lists, 1976-1990, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Literary: Notes, 1989, undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Notes (1 of 2), undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Notes (2 of 2), undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Reports, 1972-1994 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Nominating Committee, 1976-2015, undated; 15
    - Correspondence, 1976-1978 April (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1978 May-1980 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 November 28 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1984 November 30-1985 March (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1985 April (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence (1 of 4), 1985 November (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (2 of 4), 1985 November (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence (3 of 4), 1985 November (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence (4 of 4), 1985 November (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 2004 July 12-19 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 2004 July 26-27 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 2004 July 28-September (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2004 October 1-6 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2004 October 1-6 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 2004 October 11 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 2004 October 12-November (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 2004 December 1-21 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 2004 December 22-2005 January 4 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, 2005 January 5 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2005 January 6 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2005 January 6 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2005 January 12-19 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2005 January 12-19 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2005 January 20-26 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2005 January 20-26 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (1 of 3), 2005 January 26-February 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (2 of 3), 2005 January 26-February 1 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (3 of 3), 2005 January 26-February 1 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2005 February 6-9 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2005 February 6-9 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 2005 March 8-10 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 2005 March 16-April 1 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 2005 April 4-26 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 2005 April 27-29 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 2005 May, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 2014-2015 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence and Ballot Materials: Kathlene Ferris, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence and Election Materials, 2013-2014 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence and Notes, 2015 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Notes, and Reports (1 of 2), 2004-2005 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Notes, and Reports (2 of 2), 2004-2005 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Agendas and Minutes, 2014 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Agendas and Minutes, 2015 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Ballot Materials, 1990-2005 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Ballot Materials, 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Ballot Materials, 2006-2007 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Candidates, 2004-2005 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Election Materials, 2007-2015 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Election Results, 1983-1987 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Election Results, 1989-1993 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Election Results, 2016 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Literary: General, 1976-1983 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Literary: General, 2004, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Literary: General, 2012-2015 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Literary: General, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Guidelines, Notes, and Reports, 2012-2015 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Literary: Minutes from Executive Board Meetings, 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Reports, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Reports (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Reports (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Reports, 1986-2005 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Literary: Reports from Executive Board Meetings, 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Tally Sheets, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Professional Development Committee, 1972-2015, undated; 16
    - Correspondence, 1981 April-August (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1981 September-November (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1981 December 8-11 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1981 December 16-1982 January (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1982 February-June (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1982 July-October (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1982 October-December (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1984 May-November (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1984 December (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1984 December (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1989 November-1990 June (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1990 July-1991, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Chair Leslie Meyer, 2012-2013 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Society of American Archivists Course: "Inreach and Outreach for Digital Archives", 2014 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Webinar Materials, 2014 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Workshop: "Processing and Managing Congressional Papers", 2012 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Workshop Presenter Registration, 2006-2007 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and Literary, 2011-2012 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and Literary: Executive Board Meeting, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence and Notes, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence and Notes: Workshop: "After the Water Comes", 1984-1985, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence and Workshop Worksheets: "Master File", 2014 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Agreement, Manual, and Workshop Worksheets, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Dallas Workshop, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Denton Workshop, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Executive Board Meeting, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Executive Board Meetings, 2014 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Fliers and Rosters, 1981, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Galveston Workshop, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Literary: General (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Literary: General (2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Literary: General, 1989-1994, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Literary: List of Chairs and Workshops, circa 1989 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Minutes and Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Notes, 1982, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Programs, 1981-1985, undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Registration, 1985, undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Registration Materials: Workshop: "After the Water Comes", 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Literary: Victoria Workshop, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Victoria Workshop, circa 1981 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Workshop: "A Workshop on the Conservation of Books and Manuscripts", 1980 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Workshop: "Archival Box-Making", 2015 May (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Workshop: "Audiovisual Preservation for Beginners", 2015 May (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Literary: Workshop: "Becoming a Grant-Ready Institution", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Workshop: "Grant Writing Clinic", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Workshop: "Implementing MPLP [More Product, Less Process]", 2013 May (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Workshop: "Interdisciplinary Use of Manuscripts and Archives", 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Workshop: "Oral History Archives in Practice", 2013 May (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Workshop: "Planning Fundable Grants", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Workshop: "Project Management for Archivists", 2014 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Workshop: "Records Management for Archivists", 2015 May (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Workshop Guidelines (1 of 3), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Workshop Guidelines (2 of 3), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Literary: Workshop Guidelines (3 of 3), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Literary: Workshop Guidelines, 1982 April (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Literary: 2015 Workshop Plans (1 of 2), 2014-2015 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Literary: 2015 Workshop Plans (2 of 2), 2014-2015 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Workshops, 1981-2004 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Workshops, 2004-2010 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence and Forms, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Publications Committee, 1976-1995, undated; 17
    - Correspondence, 1976-1989 March (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1989 April-June (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1989 July 5-18 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1989 July 21-29 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1989 August 1-14 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1989 August 15-September 19 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1989 September 20-26 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1989 October-December (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1990 January-February (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1990 March-June (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1990 July-October (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1990 November-1991 January (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1991 March-April, undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 June (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1994 July-October (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1994 November-1995, undated (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Financial, 1985-1995 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Committee Guidelines, 1989, undated (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Literary: General, 1984-1989 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Mailing Lists, 1991, undated (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Press Releases, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- General Membership, 1970-2016, undated; 3
  Series III. General Membership contains correspondence from archivists inquiring about their membership status in SSA, various letters written about relevant political bills, essays concerning the history of the society, membership directories, newsletters, and other printed materials. There are also a number of three-dimensional artifacts that were produced for various committees and annual meetings. Overall, the series is in good condition.
  Cassette tape; Compact disk (CD); Flash memory devices; Floppy disk; Photographic print
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1974 January-July (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1974 September-1975 June (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1975 July-1976 May (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1976 June-1985, undated (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2011 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Blank Letterhead, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: C. George Younkin (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: C. George Younkin (2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: C. George Younkin, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: C. George Younkin: Creation of SSA, 1968-1972 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Hubert Humphreys, 1972-1976 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Institutional Directory, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Logo Design, 2006 February (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Mark Lambert, 1997-2004 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Political, 1979 February (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Political (1 of 2), 1979 March (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Political (2 of 2), 1979 March (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Political, 1979 March 29-May 16 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Political, 1979 May 21-1980 January 23 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Political, 1980 January 23-February 12 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Political, 1980 February 13-March 17 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Political, 1980 April 7-August 13 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Political, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Sandra Myres: Creation of SSA, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Shelly Kelly: Society of American Archivists: Spotlight Award Nomination, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Society of American Archivists, 1984-1985 March (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Society of American Archivists, 1985 July-October (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and Literary: Mark Lambert, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and Literary: Society of American Archivists Archival Symposium, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and Literary: Sandra Myres, 1972-1974 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and Literary: Sandra Myres, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and Literary: SSA Session at Texas State Historical Association Conference, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Drafts, and Forms: SSA Regional Directory (1 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Drafts, and Forms: SSA Regional Directory (2 of 2), 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Literary: 1973 Workshop Mailing List, 1970-1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Literary: Address Lists (1 of 2), 1994, undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Literary: Address Lists (2 of 2), 1994, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Literary: Ballot Materials, 1997-2004 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Literary: Blank Membership Forms, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Literary: Clippings: Creation of SSA, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Literary: Clippings: General, 1989, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Literary: Booklet: "Society of Southwest Archivists: The First Decade": Charles R. Schultz, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Literary: Booklet: "Society of Southwest Archivists: The First Two Decades": Charles R. Schultz, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 17)